# Fraser W Levack

Full Time 3rd Year Computer Science Student.

#### Contact

2/3, 50 Kelvingrove St Glasgow, G3 7RZ 07724349134

Email LinkedIn GitHub

#### Education

3<sup>rd</sup> year, BSC in Computer Science University of Glasgow

Scottish Advanced Higher A x 2 Scottish Higher A x 5 From Grove Academy Dundee

# Programming Languages

Typescript
Python
Java
C & C++
HTML & CSS

## Technologies

React
Django
Vite
Node.js, Deno & Three.js
SDL & OpenGL

#### Tools

GitHub & GitLab JetBrains IDE's WSL Unix / Ubuntu Pages & Workflows

#### About

I am a 3<sup>rd</sup> year Glasgow University undergraduate student living in Glasgow. I am an enthusiastic individual with a wide range of software experience. I have excellent communication skills and a positive attitude. My interests vary a lot, from low level programming to front end frameworks.

### Experience

AUGUST 2024 - PRESENT

Freelance Web Developer | Design for Displacement Lead developer for the Design for Displacement architecture course. Working with Typescript and React to create a stylistic, modern and informative Website.

SEPTEMBER 2024 - PRESENT

**Software Developer & Team Chair** | Off Axis Gigs Working in a team, through Glasgow Uni, to design and implement improvements to the company's current tech system.

SEPTEMBER 2020 – SEPTEMBER 2024

**Pharmacy Assistant** | Davidson's Chemists Long-term part-time job, using pharmaceutical technologies.

SEPTEMBER 2021 – JUNE 2022

**Lifeguard** | Ye Amphibious Ancients Bathing Association Dedicated pool lifeguard.

## **Projects**

Django Jam | Music Sharing

An online web-app with an interactive piano. Used to record and share Tunes with others.

C Paint | Painting Software

A program written C and using OpenGL to allow painting.

**Sled-Eval**| Evaluation Library

A C library for evaluating mathematical expressions. Detailed and easy to use.

### Awards, Societies and Hobbies

Awards: – Vice Chief Executive for MATE National Competition – World Host Principles Customer Service, – DVSA Driver's License – NPLQ Lifeguard – Grove Academy Vice School Captain

Member of: Glasgow Uni Tech, Ai, and Book Societies, V&A Dundee's Young people's collective. Some other hobbies include Surfing, Skiing and rock climbing.